DAN KLEIN: OK.
So that's CSPs.
In summary, CSPs are a very special
kind of search problem.
The states, rather than being black
boxes, are partial assignments.
And the goal test, rather than being a
black box, is defined by a collection
of constraints.
In short, because we can see this extra
information, we now have smarter
algorithms that check your
constraints as you go.
We have speed ups to the basic
backtracking search, like ordering, go
through the variables in a smart
way, and the values.
Filtering, think about the consequences
of your assignments and
propagate them forward.
Structure, exploit any kind of structure
in the constraint graph that
we know gives us an efficient
algorithm.
And then we have this new method called
iterative in conflicts, which
is often effective in practice,
though it is life on the edge.
You don't have a fringe guaranteeing
the kind of completeness that you
would have had in a standard
graph search.